[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 15, "question": "Rudy, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 16, "answer": "I'm good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 17, "question": "How are you, Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 18, "answer": "Well, I'm good, but I don't know what to make of all of this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "Right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", ":", "EX", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "Do you think there is a reasonable defense for putting into the public domain the material that he reasonably judiciously chose to put out there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "There's -- there really isn't a legal defense, there's an emotional defense.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PDT", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "Is there a public interest defense?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "You can try all that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "Is there any more that the president should be doing to try and bring him to justice?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Well, I think the president is doing everything he can to bring him to justice.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 98, "question": "-- for political gain and perhaps even intelligence?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 99, "answer": "I think we would.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "IN", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 140, "question": "To the extent that you have aided and abetted Snowden, even in his current movements, why shouldn't you, Mr. Greenwald, be charged with a crime?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 141, "answer": "I think it's pretty extraordinary that anybody who would call themself a journalist would publicly muse about whether or not other journalists should be charged with felonies.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Snowden", "Mr. Greenwald"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "Or should we just be focusing on Snowden himself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Well, I mean I think a journalist has the power and the right to ask any question that they want.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Snowden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 225, "question": "What did you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 226, "answer": "Well, first of all, if I were George Zimmerman, I would be furious at my lawyer unless the lawyer told him he was going to open with that joke.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 246, "question": "What was your reaction today to day one of this eagerly awaited Zimmerman- Trayvon trial today?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "NN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBD", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 247, "answer": "The joke was inappropriate and wasn't funny.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "Do you think that will sustain itself through the trial, or do you think inevitably it will turn into a race trial?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "I think it's hard to avoid race in this trial.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 280, "question": "Are you in the hero or villain camp?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 281, "answer": "You know, honestly, I haven't followed the case as much as others have.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 284, "question": "How much do you care about your own private data being made available to a government?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 285, "answer": "I care tremendously.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "What do you think of that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "I think that we all grow, we all develop.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 321, "question": "Nobody wants to make a decision?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 322, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "Is it an overreaction?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "I'm not so sure it is.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 351, "question": "Everything changes, but are you growing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 352, "answer": "I agree with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Fidel Castro"]}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ":", ":", "NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 361, "question": "How long could you talk for if you wanted?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "Well, I'm no Fidel Castro - (LAUGHTER)", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 406, "question": "For anybody who is looking for this, who worried about it, you know, maybe has heart issues and so on, what should they be really, really looking for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "RB", "IN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 407, "answer": "Well, the first sign which both of these cast members had, was shortness of breath.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 424, "question": "Does that have a material impact on later heart issues?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 425, "answer": "It's a risk factor for heart problems because it can damage the heart while you're taking the cocaine or doing some of these other drugs or alcohol.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "Is it genetic at all, this kind of -- this kind of heart attack?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "It is genetic, but it's only a third genetic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 471, "question": "The myth about these, and I'm told there's a myth, is that you can actually get flu or flu-like symptoms simply by having the shot, is that true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 472, "answer": "You cannot get the flu from the flu shot because the material is actually dead flu virus.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "That is a myth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "That's a myth.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 486, "question": "Does that make sense to you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "VB", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 487, "answer": "It's exactly what happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 495, "question": "Can you at least just say, \"Sorry, Piers\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJS", "RB", "VBP", ",", "``", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "''", "."], "aSentId": 496, "answer": "I'm sorry, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 504, "question": "Where do you sit with this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 505, "answer": "Well, it's an interesting perspective.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 516, "question": "Can you talk about what's been going on there for women who are watching who are curious?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "VBG", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 517, "answer": "Well, if you can keep your weight down within a reasonable amount as you get pregnant, it makes life a lot easier for you and the baby.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "CC", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "And this can be used with any game like \"Call of Duty,\" any of the popular games?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "``", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "''", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "Anything, and other systems, too.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 569, "question": "Is it working?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 570, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 635, "question": "How is that not to a disturbed mind -- and this is a sniper rifle you have, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "TO", "DT", "VBN", "NN", ":", "CC", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 636, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "VBZ", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 663, "question": "I mean, and you know, would you take that away from them, the joy of just having a little fun inside their house?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 664, "answer": "I think the argument -- the least effective argument I've heard about guns is -- especially with the AR-15s which these replicate, is they're just good fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130624pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 669, "question": "Well, when you were holding that sniper rifle, did you feel like shooting someone?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "JJR", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 670, "answer": "No, but I'm not mentally disturbed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]